(Amy:)No, I had a cover story.
I told everyone it was herpes.
- So how's everything with you and Leonard?
- I don't know. It's still kind of weird.
(Penny:)We haven't really recovered
since he proposed to me in the middle of sex.
(Amy:)Oh. Boo-hoo.
(Amy:)If Sheldon proposed to me during sex...
...my ovaries would grab onto him
and never let go.
(Sheldon:)Leonard, where do you stand
on the anthropic principle?
- Interesting question. On the one hand...
- You don't even know what it is, do you?
(Sheldon:)The anthropic principle states...
(Sheldon:)...that if we wish to explain
why our universe exists the way it does...
(Sheldon:)...the answer is that
it must have qualities...
(Sheldon:)...that allow intelligent creatures
to arise...
(Sheldon:)...who are capable of asking the question.
(Sheldon:)As I am doing so eloquently right now.
(Leonard:)I know what the anthropic principle is.
(Sheldon:)Of course.
I just explained it to you.
(Sheldon:)Now, where do you stand on it?